iphoneheat.com 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy - iPhoneHeat

At www.iPhoneHeat.com, the privacy of your personal information is of extreme importance to us.

Below we have outlined what type of personal information is received, collected when you visit iPhoneHeat.com and how we protect it. We do NOT share our visitors information with any 3rd party. If you have any question(s) please ask us via contact form.

 **Visitor Log**  
We maintain the log files to keep the information of our visitors. Information stored includes:

  * Your Computer IP address
  * ISP (internet service provider) information
  * Internet browser application (IE, Firefox, Opera etc) information, which you are using while visiting iphoneheat.com
  * Time stamp includes time when you visit our web site
  * Web Pages which are visited by you

 **Email Addresses**  
You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party.

 **Cookies**  
iPhoneHeat.com may use Web Cookies or similar technologies to manage users’ site preferences and ensure the site’s functionality. Cookies keep track of your authentication, session tracking. These just relate to your site preferences and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish. Accessing our website is not dependent of accepting cookies. This data is not shared with any third party.

iPhoneHeat.com may use different ad networks and other service providers, such as Google.com and Kontera, to help present customized content and advertisements. These providers may use cookies or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience.

iPhoneHeat.com may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as an iPhoneHeat.com user with certain ad network and service providers, including Google.com and Kontera, to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. The use of cookies or similar technologies by Google.com, Kontera, and other ad network and content providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not that of iPhoneHeat.com.

 **Legal proceedings**  
We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but iPhoneHeat.com  may need to disclose information when required by law.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
